TIFFANY SOBCZAK

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

698 Lafleur Street Sainte Genevieve, MO, 63701

PHONE

314 791 7436

EMAIL

tiff.sobczak@gmail.com

LINKS

GitHub

LinkedIn

<u>Portfolio</u>

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Node

Express

React

MongoDB

MySQL

Visual Studio Code

GitHub

Insomnia

TablePlus

PROFILE

I am a hardworking former public school teacher turned software engineer seeking full time employment. After five years of teaching I am looking for a new challenge as I start my journey as a software engineer. As a life long learner I equally enjoy tackling difficult problems independently and by collaborating with a team. I am excited to quickly learn new skills and technologies to help contribute to my team's larger goals.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Software Engineer Intern, Astral

Remote

Feb 2022 — Present

Participated in agile ceremonies. Shadowed engineers on implementation of an API developer portal service delivered via an NPM package. Created framework for validating changes to the API developer portal NPM package.

Homeroom & Math Teacher, Crandon School District

Crandon, WI

Jun 2018 — Oct 2022

Provided and differentiated both in person and virtual instruction for approximately 115 students across 4th, 7th, and 8th grade as both a Math and homeroom teacher. Provided input for curriculum planning and department restructuring. Collaborated with grade level and content area multiple Professional Learning Committees.

American History Teacher, Sikeston School District

Sikeston, MO

Oct 2016 — Jun 2018

Created and delivered American History curriculum for approximately 150 students from 9th to 12th grade. Managed a classroom web page as well as a Google Classroom. Served on the Social Studies Professional Learning Committee.

EDUCATION

Web Development Boot Camp, Washington University

Sr. Louis, MO

Oct 2021 — Apr 2022

Completed 24 week course of weekly code assignments, challenges, and 3 group projects. Learned full stack web development with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and SQL. Implemented web applications with frameworks such as React, Node/Express, and MySQL/MongoDB.

Bachelor of Science in Middle School Education, Southeast Missouri State University

Cape Girardeau, MO

Aug 2012 — May 2016

Graduated Cum Lade